Guide to the Jerome New Frank Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- CORRESPONDENCE & SUBJECTS FILE 1937-1941, Circa December 1937-Circa April 1941; Series III; 10' (24 boxes)
  - Subjects File
    - appeal from the the District Court of the United States for the District of Columbia, February 7, 1938--interpretation of the term "willfully" (Box 44, Folder 812)
    - Public Works Finance Act, 1938 (Box 44, Folder 813)
    - "Railroad Reorganization and the Bankruptcy Powers of Congress", undated (Box 44, Folder 814)
    - railroad reorganization: an act to provide for the regional consolidation of railroads, and for other purposes, 1938 (Box 44, Folder 815)
    - railroad reorganization: cumulative operating results of selected class I railways (chart), 1937-1938 (Box 44, Folder 816)
    - railroad reorganization: fragment of unidentified report, undated (Box 44, Folder 817)
    - railroad reorganization: Guide to Defaulted Railroad Bonds, 1938 (Box 44, Folder 818)
    - railroad reorganization: material relating to National Association of Railroad and Utilities Commissioners, 1938 (Box 44, Folder 819)
    - railroad reorganization: plan of reorganization for the Chicago Great Western Railroad Company, 1938 (Box 44, Folder 820)
    - railroad reorganization: statement by Burton K. Wheeler, Chairman of the Senate Interstate Commerce Committee, in connection with the report on the Seaboard Co. Ltd., 1938 (Box 44, Folder 821)
    - Regulation FA: pegging, fixing and stabilizing the prices of registered securities, 1938 (Box 44, Folder 822)
    - research material on economics for "New Book", 1934-1935, 1937-1938, undated (Box 44, Folder 823)
    - research material used by JNF in the preparation of articles and speeches, undated (Box 44, Folder 824)
    - Securities Exchange Act of 1934 and amendments, 1938 (Box 44, Folder 825)
    - Securities Violations Section Bulletin, Feb-Mar, 1939 (Box 44, Folder 826)
    - statement of Mrs. Lester Buchanan concerning Gallinger Hospital, undated (Box 44, Folder 827)
    - transcript: extract of argument before the commission (SEC) in the matter of Consumers Power Company, undated (Box 44, Folder 828)
    - transcript of the Cornerstone Ceremony of the Franklin D. Roosevelt Library, 1939 (Box 44, Folder 829)
    - Townsend v. United States, appeal from the the District Court of the United States for the District of Columbia, February 7, 1938—interpretation of the term "willfully" (Box 44, Folder 830)
    - travel orders, 1938-1939 (Box 44, Folder 831)
    - Weekly Review of Periodicals, Federal Reserve Board (two issues), 1938 (Box 44, Folder 832)
- CORRESPONDENCE & SUBJECTS FILE 1941-1957, Circa May 1941-1957; Series IV; 12' (29 boxes)
  - Correspondence
    - A, 1941-1944, 1946-1957, undated (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Abrahamsen, David, 1945 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Acheson, Dean, 1945, 1949-1950, 1952 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Adamic, Louis, 1941 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Adams, Gridley, 1947 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Adelman, S. Martin, 1950 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Adler, Mortimer J., 1955 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Agger, Carolyn E., 1942, undated (Box 45, Folder 8)
      See also: box 26, folder 224
    - Agger, E. E., 1945 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Akers, Dwight, 1941 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Alexander, Jack., 1942-1943 (Box 45, Folder 11)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 2/7
      See also: box 68, folder 817
    - Alexander, Robert J., 1951 (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Allan, George B., 1942 (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - Allen, A., 1949 (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - Allen, Florence E., 1945 (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Allen, James, 1941, 1945 (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - Allen, Robert S., 1941-1942 (Box 45, Folder 17)
    - Allorio, Enrico, 1956 (Box 45, Folder 18)
    - Allyn, Robert Starr, 1945 (Box 45, Folder 19)
    - Amadeo, Santos P., 1954 (Box 45, Folder 20)
    - American Bar Association., 1941-1947, 1949-1951, 1953-1955 (Box 45, Folder 21)
      See also: box 60, folder 597
    - American Bar Association Journal, 1941, 1945-1946 (Box 45, Folder 22)
    - American Bar Foundation, 1956 (Box 45, Folder 23)
    - American Civil Liberties Union, 1946, 1951-1952 (Box 45, Folder 24)
    - American Committee for Cultural Freedom, 1951-1953, 1955 (Box 45, Folder 25)
    - American Council for Judaism, Inc., The, 1944-1946, 1950, 1954 (Box 45, Folder 26-27)
    - American Jewish Committee, The, 1943-1945, 1947-1950, 1953-1954 (Box 45, Folder 28)
    - American Jewish Congress., 1946, 1950, 1952 1954, 1956 (Box 45, Folder 29)
      See also: box 67, folder 777
    - American Jewish Historical Society, 1948, 1952, 1954-1955 (Box 46, Folder 30)
    - American Jewish Tercentenary Committee, 1953-1954 (Box 46, Folder 31)
    - American Judicature Society, 1946, 1949 (Box 46, Folder 32)
    - The American Mercury, 1943, 1945-1946, 1950 (Box 46, Folder 33)
      See: box 46, folder 43 See: box 59, folder 562 See: box 69, folder 864
    - American Psychological Association, Inc., 1947-1948 (Box 46, Folder 34)
    - American Psychopathological Association, 1953 (Box 46, Folder 35)
    - The American Scholar, 1946-1952 (Box 46, Folder 36)
    - Americans United for World Organization, Inc., 1944-1946 (Box 46, Folder 37)
    - Ames, Louise, 1956 (Box 46, Folder 38)
    - Anderson, Clinton P., 1949 (Box 46, Folder 39)
    - Anderson, Dewey, 1948, 1950 (Box 46, Folder 40)
    - Anderson, Maxwell, 1952 (Box 46, Folder 41)
    - Anderson, Victor, 1944 (Box 46, Folder 42)
    - Angoff, Charles, 1946 (Box 46, Folder 43)
    - Ann Watkins, Inc., 1941-1943, 1945-1946 (Box 46, Folder 44)
    - Anti-Defamation League of B'nai B'rith, 1948, 1953, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 45)
    - Appleby, Paul H., 1941, 1945-1952 (Box 46, Folder 46)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 13/10
    - The Arbitration Journal, 1947, 1949 (Box 46, Folder 47)
    - Arens, Richard, 1951, 1955-1956, undated (Box 46, Folder 48)
    - Arkush, Ralph Montgomery, 1942 (Box 46, Folder 49)
    - Armstrong, Walter P., 1945 (Box 46, Folder 50)
    - Army, United States Department of the, 1943, 1949 (Box 46, Folder 51)
    - Arnold, Thurman W., 1942-1945, 1948, 1950-1951 (Box 46, Folder 52)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 15/18
    - Arnstein, Ira B., 1954 (Box 46, Folder 53)
      See also: box 74, folder 35
    - Asbill, Mac, 1953 (Box 46, Folder 54)
    - Ascher, Charles S., 1943, 1950, 1952, 1954-1955 (Box 46, Folder 55)
    - Ascoli, Max, 1948-1949 (Box 46, Folder 56)
    - Asher, Louis E., 1945 (Box 46, Folder 57)
    - Association of American Law Schools, 1945, 1952-1955 (Box 46, Folder 58)
    - Association of American Law Schools, Special Committee on Law and Psychology., 1952-1956 (Box 46, Folder 59)
      See also: box 52, folder 274 See also: box 61, folder 632 See also: box 65, folder 733
    - Association of the Bar of the City of New York, The, 1941-1943, 1945-1956 (Box 46, Folder 60)
    - Aswell, Edward C., 1941-1943, 1953 (Box 46, Folder 61)
    - The Atlantic Monthly, 1943 (Box 46, Folder 62)
      See: box 61, folder 634
    - Atomic Energy Commission, 1947 (Box 46, Folder 63)
    - Authors' Fund, Inc., 1945-1946 (Box 46, Folder 64)
    - Axtell, Silas Blake, 1945, 1957 (Box 46, Folder 65)
    - Ba-Bo, 1941-1957, undated (Box 47, Folder 66)
    - Br-By, 1941-1957, undated (Box 47, Folder 67)
    - Bachrach, Arthur C., 1941, 1946-1947 (Box 47, Folder 68)
    - Bachrach, Marion, 1948 (Box 47, Folder 69)
    - Baldwin, Roger N., 1944, 1955 (Box 47, Folder 70)
    - Baldwin (Roger N.) Civil Liberties Foundation, 1951 (Box 47, Folder 71)
    - Ballard, Betty (Mrs. Ernest), 1945, 1950 (Box 47, Folder 72)
    - Balogh, E., 1947 (Box 47, Folder 73)
    - Balsam, Solomon, 1942 (Box 47, Folder 74)
    - Bard, Ralph A., 1942 (Box 47, Folder 75)
    - Barker, Lee, 1947, 1950, 1953, 1956 (Box 47, Folder 76)
    - Barnes, John P., 1945, 1947, 1950, 1954 (Box 47, Folder 77)
    - Barnett, Harold L., 1942-1943, 1949-1950, 1956 (Box 47, Folder 78)
    - Barriger, John W., 1945 (Box 47, Folder 79)
    - Barry, John V., 1950 (Box 47, Folder 80)
    - Bass, Milton A., 1947 (Box 47, Folder 81)
    - Baukhage, H. R., 1947 (Box 47, Folder 82)
    - Bazelon, David L., 1954-1956, undated (Box 47, Folder 83)
    - Beacon Press, The, 1953-1956 (Box 47, Folder 84)
    - Beard, Charles A., 1944-1945 (Box 47, Folder 85)
    - Bebb, Herbert, 1949 (Box 47, Folder 86)
    - Beck, Thomas H., 1942 (Box 47, Folder 87)
    - Becker, Benjamin V. and Elizabeth, 1941-1942, 1944-1949, 1951, 1955 (Box 47, Folder 88)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 19-1/15
    - Becker, Emanuel, 1945 (Box 47, Folder 89)
    - Beenhouwer, Harold, 1944 (Box 47, Folder 90)
    - Bendix, Ludwig and Reinhard, 1950-1951 (Box 47, Folder 91)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 1-2/2
    - Benjamin, Alfred L., 1947, 1951 (Box 47, Folder 92)
    - Benjamin, Robert M., 1942-1943 (Box 47, Folder 93)
    - Benton, Mrs. Thomas Hart, 1942 (Box 47, Folder 94)
    - Benton, William, 1943-1946 (Box 47, Folder 95)
    - Berge, Wendell, 1944, 1954 (Box 47, Folder 96)
    - Berger, Raoul, 1942, 1944-1948, 1950, 1953 (Box 47, Folder 97)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 15/6
    - Berkowitz, David S., 1954-1955 (Box 47, Folder 98)
    - Berle, Adolph A. Jr., 1945, 1948, 1950-1951 (Box 47, Folder 99)
    - Berman, Eleanor Davidson, 1948 (Box 47, Folder 100)
    - Bernard, Viola, 1947-1948, 1952 (Box 47, Folder 101)
    - Bernays, Edward L., 1946, 1953 (Box 47, Folder 102)
    - Bessie, Simon Michael, 1947-1950 (Box 47, Folder 103)
    - Biddle, Francis, 1942-1943 (Box 47, Folder 104)
    - Biggs, John Jr., 1943, 1945, 1948, 1952, 1954 (Box 47, Folder 105)
    - Billikopf, Jacob, 1941, 1943-1947, 1949-1950, undated (Box 48, Folder 106)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 27/6
    - Bittker, Boris I., 1942-1952, 1954, 1956, undated (Box 48, Folder 107)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 43/39
      See also: box 117, folder 1141 See also: box 91, folder 742 See also: box 178, folder 1
    - Black, Hugo L., 1941, 1943, 1945-1946, 1948-1956, undated (Box 48, Folder 108)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 22/23
    - Blair, Paxton, 1942 (Box 48, Folder 109)
    - Blair-Smith, Robert M., 1942, 1944 (Box 48, Folder 110)
    - Blaisdell, Thomas, 1945 (Box 48, Folder 111)
    - Bliven, Bruce, 1946-1947, 1950 (Box 48, Folder 112)
    - Blum, Asher, 1942 (Box 48, Folder 113)
    - Bodenheimer, Edgar, 1950-1951 (Box 48, Folder 114)
    - Bok, Curtis, 1943, 1946-1947, 1949 (Box 48, Folder 115)
    - Bondy, William., 1942, 1949 (Box 48, Folder 116)
      See also: box 115, folder 1123
    - Bone, Homer T., 1941-1942, 1944-1947 (Box 48, Folder 117)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 13/9
    - Boorstin, Daniel J., 1945, 1948 (Box 48, Folder 118)
    - Borchard, Edwin M., 1942-1943, 1945, 1947 (Box 48, Folder 119)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 15/11
    - Borkin, Joseph, 1942, 1955 (Box 48, Folder 120)
    - Botein, Bernard, 1945, 1952, 1956 (Box 48, Folder 121)
    - Bowen, Katherine Drinker, 1951 (Box 48, Folder 122)
    - Bowles, Chester, 1945, 1948 (Box 48, Folder 123)
    - Braden George D., 1947-1948, 1950-1951, 1954 (Box 48, Folder 124)
    - Bradley, F. X. Jr., 1950-1951 (Box 48, Folder 125)
    - Brandeis University, 1952-1955, undated (Box 48, Folder 126)
    - Bright, John., 1943, 1946, 1948 (Box 48, Folder 127)
    - Bronx County Bar Association, 1946-1948, 1951, 1954 (Box 48, Folder 128)
    - Brooklyn Law Review, 1948-1949, 1954 (Box 48, Folder 129)
    - Brooklyn Lawyers Club, 1952-1953, 1956-1957 (Box 48, Folder 130)
    - Brooks, Cleanth, 1952, 1954 (Box 48, Folder 131)
    - Brown, Francis, 1949-1950, 1956 (Box 48, Folder 132)
    - Brown, John Cotton, 1954 (Box 48, Folder 133)
    - Brown, Louis M., 1956 (Box 48, Folder 134)
    - Brown, Ralph Sharp Jr., 1948, 1956 (Box 48, Folder 135)
    - Brown, Robert P., 1956 (Box 48, Folder 136)
    - Brownell, Herbert Jr., 1954 (Box 48, Folder 137)
    - Brutau, Jose Puig, 1955-1956 (Box 48, Folder 138)
    - Burke, Kenneth, 1942-1943, 1946, 1951 (Box 48, Folder 139)
    - Burnett, Whit, 1945 (Box 48, Folder 140)
    - Burr, H. S., 1955 (Box 48, Folder 141)
    - Byerly, Robert W., 1945 (Box 48, Folder 142)
    - Byrnes, James F., 1942, undated (Box 48, Folder 143)
    - Ca-Cl, 1942-1943, 1945-1947, 1949-1957, undated (Box 48, Folder 144)
    - Co-Cu, 1941-1943, 1945-1956, undated (Box 49, Folder 145)
    - Cades, J. Russell, 1950 (Box 49, Folder 146)
    - Cahn, Edmond N., 1946-1953 (Box 49, Folder 147)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 48/35
    - Cahn, Edmond N., 1954-1957, undated (Box 49, Folder 148)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 60/46
    - Cairns, Huntington, 1942, 1946-1950 (Box 49, Folder 149)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 26/15
    - California Law Review, 1949-1950 (Box 49, Folder 150)
    - Canfield, Cass, 1952 (Box 49, Folder 151)
    - Carr, Robert K., 1951 (Box 49, Folder 152)
    - Case and Comment, 1953-1954 (Box 49, Folder 153)
    - Cassin, Edward, 1947 (Box 49, Folder 154)
    - Celler, Emanuel, 1942, 1948, 1950, 1955-1956 (Box 49, Folder 155)
    - Chafee, Z. Jr., 1952 (Box 49, Folder 156)
    - Chamberlain, John, 1945, 1950-1951 (Box 49, Folder 157)
    - Chandler, Henry P., 1941 (Box 49, Folder 158)
      See also: box 118, folder 1142-1146
    - Chapin, Thomas C., 1949 (Box 49, Folder 159)
    - Chapman, Oscar L., 1948-1949 (Box 49, Folder 160)
    - Chase, Harrie Brigham., 1941-1954 (Box 49, Folder 161)
      See: box 91, folder 742 See: box 117, folder 1141
    - Chase, John W., 1948-1949 (Box 49, Folder 162)
    - Chase, Stuart, 1943, 1945 (Box 49, Folder 163)
    - Cheatham, Elliott E., 1942-1943, 1945, 1955, undated (Box 49, Folder 164)
    - Chenery, William L., 1943 (Box 49, Folder 165)
    - Chicago Law Review, The University of, 1941-1942, 1945-1949, 1953-1954 (Box 49, Folder 166)
      See also: box 51, folder 237
    - Chicago Law School, University of., 1944-1945, 1947, 1949, 1951-1956 (Box 49, Folder 167)
      See also: box 57, folder 474 See also: box 59, folder 529
    - Chicago Medical School, The, 1950-1954 (Box 49, Folder 168)
    - Chicago Press, The University of, 1948-1949, 1952 (Box 49, Folder 169)
    - Chicago, University of, 1941-1944, 1946-1947, 1953 (Box 49, Folder 170)
    - Cincinnati, University of, College of Law, 1951, 1953 (Box 49, Folder 171)
    - Citizens' Committee on Children of New York City, Inc., 1952-1956 (Box 49, Folder 172)
      See also: box 59, folder 533
    - Civil Service Commission, 1942-1944, 1956 (Box 50, Folder 173)
    - Clark, Bennett C., 1945 (Box 50, Folder 174)
    - Clark, Charles Edward., 1941-1957 (Box 50, Folder 175)
      See: box 23, folder 112 box 91, folder 742 box 117, folder 1141
    - Clark, Samuel O., 1941-1942, 1948 (Box 50, Folder 176)
    - Clark, Tom C., 1946-1947, 1957, undated (Box 50, Folder 177)
    - Clay, Cassius M., undated (Box 50, Folder 178)
    - Cleary, Edward W., 1948, 1952 (Box 50, Folder 179)
    - Cohen, Benjamin V., 1941-1942, 1945-1946, 1948, 1950, undated (Box 50, Folder 180)
    - Cohen, Boaz, 1955 (Box 50, Folder 181)
    - Cohen, Elliot E., 1948-1950, 1953, undated (Box 50, Folder 182)
    - Cohen, Felix S. and Lucy K., 1941-1943, 1946, 1948, 1950, 1952, 1954 (Box 50, Folder 183)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 5-1/10
    - Cohen, Julius, 1948, 1950, 1952, 1954, 1956 (Box 50, Folder 184)
    - Cohen, Morris Raphael, 1941-1943 (Box 50, Folder 185)
    - Cohn, Albert, 1948-1950 (Box 50, Folder 186)
    - Cohn, Herbert B. and Kathryn (Cordell), 1941-1942 (Box 50, Folder 187)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 3-1/1
    - Cole, K. C., 1950 (Box 50, Folder 188)
    - Cole, Leon, 1941, 1945, 1951, 1953 (Box 50, Folder 189)
    - Coleman, Samuel C., 1942, 1945 (Box 50, Folder 190)
    - Coleman, William C., 1942-1943, 1945 (Box 50, Folder 191)
      See also: box 57, folder 452 See also: box 61, folder 628 See also: box 64, folder 725 See also: box 68, folder 816 See also: box 118, folders 1142-1146
    - Collier's, 1943, 1945-1946, 1949-1951 (Box 50, Folder 192)
      See also: box 49, folder 165
    - Columbia Broadcasting System, Inc., 1944-1945, 1948-1949, 1954 (Box 50, Folder 193)
    - Columbia Law Review, 1941-1943, 1946-1948, 1950-1952, 1954, 1956 (Box 50, Folder 194)
    - Columbia University, 1945-1952, 1954 (Box 50, Folder 195)
    - Columbia University Libraries, 1941-1942, 1946-1949, 1951 (Box 50, Folder 196)
    - Columbia University Oral History Project, 1950-1952 (Box 50, Folder 197)
    - Cominsky, J. R., 1945-1946 (Box 50, Folder 198)
    - Commager, Henry Steele, 1943 (Box 50, Folder 199)
    - Commentary, 1945-1946, 1948-1950, 1953, undated (Box 50, Folder 200)
      See also: box 50, folder 182 See also: box 54, folder 354 See also: box 58, folder 495
    - Common Sense, 1945 (Box 50, Folder 201)
      See: box 56, folder 410
    - Compton, Charles H., 1955 (Box 50, Folder 202)
    - Conference on Science, Philosophy and Religion, 1943-1944, 1947, 1951 (Box 50, Folder 203)
    - Conference on the Scientific Spirit and Democratic Faith., 1943-1944, 1946-1947, 1949 (Box 50, Folder 204)
      See also: box 62, folder 643
    - Conger, Edward A., 1944, 1950 (Box 50, Folder 205)
    - Conn, Margaret, 1951 (Box 50, Folder 206)
    - Conrad, Alfred, 1952 (Box 50, Folder 207)
    - Constable, George W., 1951 (Box 50, Folder 208)
    - Consultative Council of Jewish Organizations, 1951, 1953 (Box 50, Folder 209)
    - Cook, Alfred A., 1946 (Box 50, Folder 210)
    - Cooke, Morris Llewellyn, 1945 (Box 50, Folder 211)
    - Cooper, Irving Ben, 1953, 1955 (Box 50, Folder 212)
    - Corcoran, Thomas Gardiner, 1941-1942, 1945-1948 (Box 51, Folder 213)
    - Cornell Law Quarterly, 1950, 1952-1955 (Box 51, Folder 214)
    - Corwin, Edward S., undated (Box 51, Folder 215)
    - Cossio, Carlos, 1948-1950 (Box 51, Folder 216)
    - Costikyan, Edward N., 1953 (Box 51, Folder 217)
    - Countryman, Vern, 1956 (Box 51, Folder 218)
    - Cousins, Norman, 1945-1946, 1948-1949, 1956 (Box 51, Folder 219)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 5/17
    - Cowan, Arthur W. A., 1943-1945, 1947-1951, undated (Box 51, Folder 220)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 38/13
    - Cowan, Thomas A., 1948-1949 (Box 51, Folder 221)
    - Coward-McCann, Inc., 1942, 1947-1950, 1952, 1954-1956 (Box 51, Folder 222)
    - Cox, Archibald, 1945, 1947 (Box 51, Folder 223)
    - Cox, Oscar, 1942-1943, 1954 (Box 51, Folder 224)
    - Coxe, Alfred C., 1942-1943, 1951 (Box 51, Folder 225)
      See: box 115, folder 1123 See: box 91, folder 742
    - Coy, Wayne, 1942 (Box 51, Folder 226)
    - Cozart, Reed., 1956 (Box 51, Folder 227)
      See also: box 51, folder 254
    - Cuneo, Ernest, 1945-1948, 1955 (Box 51, Folder 228)
    - Currie, Brainerd., 1955 (Box 51, Folder 229)
      See also: box 58, folder 516
    - Currie, Lauchlin., 1946-1948 (Box 51, Folder 230)
      See also: box 72, folder 955
    - Cutler, A. S., 1948-1949 (Box 51, Folder 231)
    - D, 1941-1947, 1949-1956 (Box 51, Folder 232)
    - Dann, Sol. A., 1947 (Box 51, Folder 233)
    - Davenport, Russell W., 1941, 1944 (Box 51, Folder 234)
    - Davis, Kenneth Culp, 1941-1942, 1955 (Box 51, Folder 235)
    - Davis, Miller, 1941, 1944-1948 (Box 51, Folder 236)
    - Davis, Sidney Martin., 1942, 1944-1946, 1948, 1953-1956, undated (Box 51, Folder 237)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 19/29
      See also: box 48, folder 107
    - Dekker, Herman, 1946 (Box 51, Folder 238)
    - Demos, Raphael, 1948 (Box 51, Folder 239)
    - Dempsey, William J., 1943-1945 (Box 51, Folder 240)
    - Denman, William., 1947, 1956 (Box 51, Folder 241)
      See also: box 52, folder 258 See also: box 126, folder 1218
    - DeSaram, John, 1956, undated (Box 51, Folder 242)
    - Desmond, Charles S., 1944-1945, 1947, 1956 (Box 51, Folder 243)
    - Desmond, Thomas C., 1948, 1950 (Box 51, Folder 244)
    - Dession, George and Poca, 1948, 1950 (Box 51, Folder 245)
    - Detzer, Dorothy, 1941 (Box 51, Folder 246)
    - Dewey, Thomas E., 1949, 1951 (Box 51, Folder 247)
    - Dial Press Inc., The, 1945-1946, 1948-1949 (Box 51, Folder 248)
    - Dickinson, John, 1949 (Box 51, Folder 249)
    - Dillard, Hardy C., 1950, 1955 (Box 51, Folder 250)
      See also: box 65, folder 751
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson, 1951 (Box 51, Folder 251)
    - Dodd, Mead & Company, 1947 (Box 51, Folder 252)
    - Domke, Martin., 1955 (Box 51, Folder 253)
      See also: box 46, folder 47
    - Donnelly, Richard C., 1952, 1956 (Box 51, Folder 254)
      See also: box 51, folder 227
    - Donovan, Patricia, 1942, 1947 (Box 51, Folder 255)
    - Donovan, William J., 1956 (Box 51, Folder 256)
    - Doubleday & Company, Inc., 1947-1948, 1952-1953 (Box 52, Folder 257)
      See also: box 47, folder 76
    - Douglas, William Orville., 1941-1951, 1953-1956, undated (Box 52, Folder 258)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 48/74
    - Downey, Sheridan, 1941 (Box 52, Folder 259)
    - Doyle, Denis P. S. (with an article by Mary Conan Doyle), 1942 (Box 52, Folder 260)
    - Driver, Sam M., 1950 (Box 52, Folder 261)
    - Drummond, Roscoe, 1945 (Box 52, Folder 262)
    - Dudley, Pendleton, 1941, 1943, 1948 (Box 52, Folder 263)
    - Duffy, Peggy, 1941, 1944 (Box 52, Folder 264)
    - Dukeminier, Jesse J. Jr., 1951, 1953-1954, 1956 (Box 52, Folder 265)
    - Dulles, John Foster, 1941-1942, 1947 (Box 52, Folder 266)
    - Dunham, William H., 1953, 1956 (Box 52, Folder 267)
    - E, 1941-1945, 1949-1953, 1956 (Box 52, Folder 268)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF:
    - Eastman, Max, 1941, 1943-1944, 1949-1950, 1956 (Box 52, Folder 269)
    - Eastman, Samuel E., 1950 (Box 52, Folder 270)
    - Ebb, Lawrence F. and Carmel (Prashker), 1945, 1947-1948, 1950, 1955-1956, undated (Box 52, Folder 271)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 1-7/6
    - Eccles, Marriner S., 1941-1942 (Box 52, Folder 272)
    - Edgerton, Henry W., 1941 (Box 52, Folder 273)
    - Ehrenzweig, Albert A., 1950-1951, 1955-1956 (Box 52, Folder 274)
      See also: box 46, folder 59
    - Eicher, Edward C., 1941-1942, 1944 (Box 52, Folder 275)
    - Einstein, Albert, 1945, 1947 (Box 52, Folder 276)
    - Eisenstein, Louis, 1946, 1956 (Box 52, Folder 277)
    - Elias, Peter, 1949 (Box 52, Folder 278)
    - Eliot, Martha M., 1953-1954 (Box 52, Folder 279)
    - Embree, Edwin R., 1944 (Box 52, Folder 280)
      See also: box 67, folder 793
    - Emory University, Journal of Public Law, 1955 (Box 52, Folder 281)
    - Encyclopaedia Brittanica, 1945-1947 (Box 52, Folder 282)
    - Epstein, Henry and Ethel S., 1941-1942, 1944-1945, 1953 (Box 52, Folder 283)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 6-3/7
    - Ernst, George G., 1942-1943 (Box 52, Folder 284)
    - Ernst, Morris L., 1941-1956 (Box 52, Folder 285)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 60/33
      See also: box 113, folder 1098
    - Erroll, David D., 1950 (Box 52, Folder 286)
    - Espy, Willard R., 1945-1946, 1950 (Box 52, Folder 287)
    - Evans, Ernestine, undated (Box 52, Folder 288)
    - Evans, Evan A., 1942-1945 (Box 52, Folder 289)
      See also: box 96, folder 833
    - Ewing, Oscar R., 1948-1949 (Box 52, Folder 290)
      See also: box 62, folder 649
    - Ezekial, Mordecai, 1954-1955 (Box 52, Folder 291)
    - F, 1941-1955, undated (Box 52, Folder 292)
    - Fadiman, Clifton, 1944 (Box 53, Folder 293)
    - Fanelli, Joseph A., 1945 (Box 53, Folder 294)
    - Farrar, John, 1946, 1948 (Box 53, Folder 295)
    - Farrar, Straus and Company, Inc., 1946 (Box 53, Folder 296)
      See also: box 53, folder 295 See also: box 70, folder 882
    - Federal Bar Association, 1941-1942, 1944, 1948, 1954 (Box 53, Folder 297)
    - Federal Bar Association of New York, New Jersey and Connecticut, 1943, 1945-1946, 1949, 1951-1954 (Box 53, Folder 298)
    - Fee, James Alger, 1949-1950 (Box 53, Folder 299)
    - Feibleman, James, 1947-1950, 1953, 1955-1956 (Box 53, Folder 300)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 16/10
    - Feller, Abraham, 1948-1949 (Box 53, Folder 301)
    - Field, Richard H., 1955 (Box 53, Folder 302)